Peyton Rous Papers 1909-1970 Mss.B.R77
American Philosophical Society
Addis, Thomas, 1881-1949; American Cancer Society.; Andrewes, C.H. (Christopher Howard), Sir; Baudisch, Oskar; Bayne-Jones, Stanhope, 1888-1970; Beard, Joseph W., 1901-; Berenblum, Isaac, 1903-; Blankenhorn, Marion Arthur, 1885-1957; Bronk, Detlev W., (Detlev Wulf), 1897-1975; Cattell, James McKeen, 1860-1944; Century Association (New York, N.Y.); Compton, Arthur Holly, 1892-1962; Corner, George Washington, 1889-1981; Crutcher, Katherine G.; Cutler, Richard B.; Dean, Henry R.; DeMaeyer, E. M.; Dolman, Claude E., (Claude Ernest), 1906-1994; Dubos, René J. (René Jules), 1901-; Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology.; Flexner, Simon, 1863-1946; Gasser, Herbert Spencer, 1888-1963; Gilding, Henry P.; Gregg, Alan, 1890-1957; Gye, Will E.; Hevesy, Georg von, 1885-1966; Huggins, Charles Brenton, 1901-; Johnson, Earl; Karsner, Howard Thomas, b. 1879; Kidd, John Graydon, 1908-; Krumbhaar, E. B., (Edward Bell), 1882-1966; Landsteiner, Karl, 1868-1943; Lipschutz, Alexander; Loeb, Leo, 1869-1959; LuckGe, Baldwin; MacNider, William de Berniere, 1881-1951; McDermott, Walsh, 1909-; Mooser, Hermann; National Academy of Sciences, Washington, D.C.; New York Academy of Medicine.; Osler, William, Sir, 1849-1919; Paul Ehrlich Stiftung; Robertson, O. H. (Oswald Hope), 1886-1966; Rockefeller Institute.; Rogers, E. Stanfield; Royal Society of Medicine Foundation.; Shope, Richard E., (Richard Edwin), 1901-; Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research.; Smith, Frederick; Stanley, Wendell Meredith, 1932-; TenBroeck, Carl, 1885-1966; Warthin, Aldred Scott, 1866-1931; Whipple, George Hoyt, 1878-; Wyckoff, Ralph W. G. (Ralph Walter Graystone), 1897-; Zinsser, Hans, 1878-1940; Articles; Blood banks; Blood--Research; Cancer--Research; Journal of Experimental Medicine; Lectures; Medical sciences; Medicine, Experimental; Medicine--Research; Medicine--Research--Finance; Nobel Prize; Pathology; Photographs; Science publishing.; Viruses; World War, 1914-1918--Medical care
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1917-1970; 47.0 Linear feet (Box 1-85)
  Scope and Contents note
  The correspondence series documents the full range of Peyton Rous's professional interests from the time of his early work on the preservation of blood during the First World War through his work on the viral theory of cancer and beyond. Among Rous's more prolific correspondents were his colleagues at the Rockefeller, Simon Flexner, Herbert Gasser, and Richard Shope, and his collaborators Stansfield Rogers and John G. Kidd. Other major correspondents include:
  Thomas Addis
  Christopher H. Andrewes
  Oscar Baudish
  Joseph W. Beard
  Isaac Berenblum
  Marion Arthur Blankenhorn
  Detlev W. Bronk
  James M. Cattell
  Arthur Holly Compton
  George W. Corner
  Kathrine G. Crutcher
  Richard B. Cutler
  Henry R. Dean
  Edward De Maeyer
  Claude E. Dolman
  René J. Dubos
  Henry P. Gilding
  Alan Gregg
  Will E. Gye
  George de Hevesy
  Charles B. Huggins
  Earl Johnson
  Howard T. Karsner
  Edward B. Krumbhaar
  Karl Landsteiner
  Alexander Lipschutz
  Leo Loeb
  Baldwin Lucké
  Walsh McDermott
  William de B. MacNider
  Hermann Mooser
  William Osler
  Paul Ehrlich Stiftung
  Frederick Smith
  Wendell M. Stanley
  Carl TenBroeck
  Aldred Scott Warthin
  George H. Whipple
  William H. Woglom
  Hans Zinsser
  Ralph W. Wyckoff
  Apart from correspondence, per se, the series includes a number of papers written by Rous, generally later in his career, and a partial run of progress reports on his research at the Rockefeller. His administrative commitments generated significant materials documenting his work with Jane Coffin Childs Memorial Fund, the National Academy of Sciences, and the Rockefeller Institute, among other organizations.
  The series also includes a particularly extensive set of materials relating to Rous's work as editor of the Journal of Experimental Medicine, correspondence relating to and letters of congratulation from a variety of colleagues on Rous's Nobel Prize, and a series of papers and talks written by Rous. The photographs in the collection (filed within the series under "Photographs") include a number of images used in Rous's publications, plus a small number of images of Rous and colleagues. Among the latter are studio portraits of Robert G. Green, Albert Baird Hastings, Karl Landsteiner, and Theobald Smith, two images of Rous (ca.1940s or 1950s), and a photograph of the Board of Directors of the Rockefeller Institute, ca.1907-1908, including Simon Flexner, T. M. Prudden, Emmett Holt, William H. Welch, Theobald Smith, Christian Herter, and Herman M. Biggs.
  - Aaser, E.
  - Abbott, A. C.
  - Abbott, G. K.
  - Abbott, Maude
  - Abbott Laboratories
  - Abercrombie, Ronald T
  - Abramson, Harold A
  - Académie Nationale de Medécine:
    - Nicole-Genty, G
  - Academy of Achievement
  - Accident - Automobile
  - Acheson, G H
  - Adair, Frank E
  - Adams, Mrs.
  - Adams, K M
  - Adams, Phillip E
  - Addis, Thomas
  - Adrian, Edgar Douglas, baron:
    - Robertson, Mrs. J
  - Agostini, Roy T
  - Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Agur, Amram
  - Ahlström, C G
  - Ahrens, E H., Jr.
  - Albert Einstein Medical Center
  - Alexander-Jackson, Eleanor
  - Alexander, Jerome
  - Alexenberg, Melvin L
  - Allee, W. C.
  - Allen, Mrs. Brown M
  - Allen, Edgar
  - Allen, Mrs. Helen
  - Allen, Raymond A.:
    - Rivers, Thomas M
  - Allison, A C
  - Almeida, June D
  - Almog, Yehuda
  - Aloe, A. S., Company:
    - Hunsaker, G
  - Alpha Omega Alpha
  - Alsberg, Carl L
  - Alsever, John B
  - Altenburg, Edgar
  - Altshuler, Charles H
  - Amberg, Samuel
  - Amberson, J Burns, Jr.
  - Ambrus, Julian
  - American Association for Cancer Research
  - American Association for Medical Progress,Inc.
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science.
  - American Association of Blood Banks
  - American Association of Immunologists (Beard and Wyckoff)
    See: Coca, Arthur F
    TenBroeck, Carl
    Rivers, Thomas M
    Berry, George Packer
    Beard, Joseph W
    Wyckoff, Ralph W.G.
  - American Association of Pathologists and Bacteriologists.
  - American Association of the History of Medicine.
  - American Cancer Society.
  - American Committee for Emigré Scholars, Writers and Artists, Inc. ( In re Mrs. Lubow Zafiowski)
  - American Committee for the Weizmann Institute of Science
    See also Weizmann Institute
    - Brainin, Joseph
    - Stone, Dewey D
  - American Express Company
  - American Foundation Studies in Government
  - American Medical Association
  - American Men of Science
  - American Mothers Committee, Inc.
  - American Philosophical Society
  - American Physicians' Art Association
  - American Public Health Association, Inc.
  - American Red Cross.
  - American Scientist
  - American Society for Experimental Pathology:
    - Long, Esmond R
    - McManus, J F A
    - Wilgram, George F
    - Stowell, Robert E
    - Dunlap, Charles E
  - American Society for Microbiology
    - Sarber, R W
    - Housewright, R D
    - Sarles, W B
    - Wyss, O
    - Gerhardt, Philip
  - The American Society for the Control of Cancer, Inc.
  - American Society of Experimental Pathologists
  - The American Spectator, Inc.
  - Amies, C Russell
  - Amoss, Harold
  - Anderson, Mary R
  - Anderson, Rudolph J
  - Andersons' Rubber Company Ltd.
  - Andervont, Howard B
  - Andresen, Julius
  - Andrewes, Christopher H
    - "Evidence for the Presence of Virus in a Non-Filterable Tar Sarcoma of the Fowl"
    - Latent Virus Infectious and Their Possible Relevance to the Cancer Problem
  - Andrewes, F W
  - Andrus, William DeWitt
  - Andrus, William DeWitt, Scholarship
  - Angevine, D Murray
  - Angus, C Franklin
  - Angus Memorial Fund
  - Anitschkow, N
  - Anitschkoff, N
  - Annual Review of Physiology
  - Ansher, Richard
  - Anson, M L
  - Antapol, William S
  - Anthony, Elli
  - Anthony, H E
  - Antivivisection
  - Appel, John
  - Arches of Science Award
  - Archibald, R M
  - Argosy Book Store, Inc.
  - The Arlington Chemical Company
  - Armstrong, Arnold
  - Armstrong, Charles
  - Armstrong, W H
  - Army Institute of Pathology Vorder
    - Brugge, Colin F
    - Dart, Raymond O
  - Arrow, G. H.
  - Aschoff, L
  - Ashby, Winifred M
  - Assistants
    - Baas - Becking, L G M
      - Drury, Dr.
    - Barach
    - Bayne-Jones, S
      - Friedewald
      - Bunting, Henry
    - Beattie, William W
      - Oertel, Horst
      - Smith, Edric B
    - Benditt, Earl P
      - Huggins, Charles
    - Berry, George Packer
    - Binger, Carl
      - Dick, MacDonald
    - Blankenhorn, M A
    - Blish, Eleanor
    - Bliss
      - Flexner, Simon
    - Bloom, William
    - Bloomfield, Arthur L
    - Blumfield, Arthur L
    - Bronner, Prof.
      - Okuneff
    - Broun, Goronwy O
      - Briggs, A P
      - Mezera, Raymond
    - Burns, Edward L
    - Clarkson, Sallie
      - Warthin, A S
    - Collier
      - McCann, William S
    - Dieuaide, Francis R
      - Robinson, G Canby
    - Dow, Robert S
    - Drury, D R
      - Oliver, Jean
      - Addis, J
      - Hewlett, A W
      - Young, S W
      - Manwaring, W H
      - Smith, E B
    - Elman, Robert
      - Morton, John
      - Amoss, Harold L
      - Dandy, Walter E
      - Graham, Evarts A
      - Weed, Lewis H
    - Forester, Charles F
      - Appleget, Thomas Baird
      - Mayer, Edwin B
    - Friedewald, William F
    - Furth, Jacob
    - Gantt, W Horsley
      - Pearce, Richard M
      - Flexner, Simon
    - Gay, Frederick P
    - Green, Robert G
    - Guthrie, Clyce Graham
    - Hamer, Richard B
    - Hamperl, Herwig
    - Hanford, John M
    - Hicks, Samuel P
      - Furth, Jacob
    - Higgins
      - Blankenhorn
      - Flexner, Simon
    - Huggins, Charles B
    - Jablons, Benjamin
      - Wood, F C
    - Karsner, Howard T
    - Klein
      - Edmunds, C W
    - Kliene Berger-Nobel
      - Emmy
    - Laubhan, R K
      - Murphy, James B
    - Lewis, Alvin E
    - Livingston, R G
    - McCann, William S
    - Mezera, Raymond A
      - Gye, W E
      - Smith, Edric B
      - French, A James
      - Robinson, Elliott S
      - Bayne-Jones, S
      - Conard, Robert
    - Moore, Robert A
    - New Men
    - Oliver, Jean
      - Flexner, Simon
    - Olms, James S
      - Burns, Edward L
      - Doull, James A
      - Hoerr, Normand L
      - Karsner, Howard T
      - Smith, E B
      - Thompson, Randall L
    - Paul, John R
    - Peabody, Francis
    - Reiss, R S
      - Smith, E B
    - Reznikoff, Paul
      - Dubois, Eugene
    - Robinson, G C
    - Rogers, Stanfield
      - Forbus, Wiley D
      - Queen, Frank B
      - Smith, Edric B
      - Sprunt, Douglas H
    - Rountree, L G
    - Rusch, Harold P
      - Bain, James
    - Sellards, A W
    - Smith, Frederick
      - Henry, James P
    - Smith, H P
    - Smith, William E
      - Bauer, Walter
      - Dienes, Louis
      - Robertson, A D
      - Gasser, Herbert S
      - Chesney, Alan M
    - Stone, Harvey B
    - Thayer, William S
    - Tullis, James R
    - Tyzzer, E E
    - Von Glahn, William C
    - Warthin, A S
    - Wilson, Hugh
      - Queen, Frank B
    - Winternitz, M C
    - Wolbach, S B
    - Wu, S D
      - Cannon, Paul R
      - Robertson, O
      - Moore, Robert A
    - Checklist of References (i.e., sources for suggesting applicants) and form letter sent to references, 1930-1931
    - Circular Letter
  - Associated Hospital Service of New York
  - The Association of American Physicians
  - Astbury, William T
  - The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company
  - Atchley, William A
  - Atlee, H B
  - Atoms for Peace Awards
  - Atwood, E V
  - Aub, Joseph C
  - Auchincloss, Hugh
  - Aver, John
  - Auerbach, Mitchel D
  - Austin, J Harold
  - from Austin, James H to the Journal of Experimental Medicine
  - The Automobile Club of America
  - Avery, Oswald T
  - Avery, John D
  - Avery, O T
  - Oswald Theodore Avery Memorial Gateway Fund.
  - Awards
    - Alvarez, Walter C
    - Parker, Mark S
    - Spies, Tom D
    - Walters, Waltman
  - Aydelotte, Frank
  - N W Ayer and Son, Inc.
  - Babbitt, Dorothea
  - Babbott, Frank Lusk
  - Babkin, B P
  - Backus, Bill
  - Bacon, George R
  - Baden, Howard P
  - Baer, Rudolf L
  - Baetjer, Howard
  - Baggenstoss, A H
  - Bailey, Alfred M
  - Bailey, Vernon:
    see also - Ten Broeck, C., and Sawyer, W. A.
  - Baints, H V
  - Baitsell, George A
  - Baker, G A
  - Baker, Newton D
  - Baker, Mrs. Rachel
  - Balducci, Diego
  - Baldwin, Horace S
  - Baldwin, J F
  - Ballance, Sir Charles
  - Baltimore Storage Co.
  - Bang, Frederik B
  - Bangham, Alec Douglas
  - Banting, Frederick G
  - Barach, Alvan L
  - Barbour, Henry G
  - Barbour, Robert W
  - Barcroft, Joseph
  - Barker, Miss Grace
  - Barlowski, Marya
  - Barnes, Henry B
  - Barnes, Stanley
  - Barnett, Mrs. J
  - Barr, David P
  - Barrett, Morris K
  - Barrett Company
  - Bartfield, Harry
  - Barto, Elizabeth
  - Barton, Paul
  - Bashford, E F
  - Bate, F J, Jr.
  - Bate, Fred, Jr.
  - Bates & Schoonmaker
  - Batson, O V
  - Baudisch, Oskar
  - Bauer, Karl H
  - Baumgartner, Leona
  - Bayless, William A
  - Bayazid, Mrs.
  - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
  - Bayne-Jones, Mrs. Stanhope
  - Bayon, H P
  - Bazett, H C
  - Bean, Marshall E
  - Bean, R Bennett
  - Bean, William B
  - Beard, Joseph W
  - Beard, P J
  - Bearn, Alexander G
  - Beaton, Mrs. Elizabeth
  - Beaton, Lindsay E
  - Beattie, W W
  - Beck, Henry A
  - Beckman, Arthur
  - Beclere, Antoine
  - Beclere, Antoinette
  - Bedouce
  - Beeson, Paul
  - Beecher, Willard
  - Begg, R W
  - Behan, R J
  - Behrman, Stanley J
  - Bell, W B
  - Belonowsky, Georges
  - Bender, C E
  - Bendixen, Hans Jorgen
  - Benedict, Stanley R
  - Benison, Saul
  - Benjamin, Bernard
  - Bennet, E A
    - Galdston, Iago, 1954
  - Bennett, H Stanley
  - Bensley, R R
  - Bentley, William A
  - Berberich, Joseph
  - Berenblum, Isaac
  - Berengaria (Ship)
    - First Class Pamphlets
  - Berg, Roland H
  - Berger, A L
  - Berglund, Hilding
  - Bergmann, Max
  - Bergmann, Werner
  - Berle, Adolph
  - Berle, Beatrice
  - Berlinghof, G J
  - Bernhard, Carl Gustaf
  - Bernhard, W
  - Berry, George Packer
  - Bertner Award
  - Bertner Foundation (R. Lee Clark)
  - Bessis, Marcel C
  - Bett, W R
  - Beutner, R, 1935
    See also: Flexner, Simon
    Barbour, Henry G.
    Moore, John Walker (copy of letter to John J. Abel)
    Clowes, G H A
  - Beveridge, W I B
  - Bewkes, Eugene G
  - Bianchi, L Chieco
  - Bibby, Mrs. Gladys
  - Biberstein, Hans H
  - Bibliography
  - Bielsohowsky, M
  - Biemiller, Ray
  - Bigger, G G
  - Bigger, J W
  - Bile
    See: Halsted, W.S. 1921-1922
    Joslin, E.P. 1924
    Judd, E. Starr 1922
    Lusk, Graham 1922
    Meyer, K. F. 1920-1923
  - Belkin, Morris
  - Billingham, Rupert E
  - Bing, Richard J
  - Binger, Carl
  - Binger, Mrs. Chloe
  - Binger, Walter D
  - Biographical Dictionary of American Men of Science
  - Biographical Encyclopedia of America
  - Biological Photographic Association, Inc.
  - Biological Abstracts
    - Friedenwald, William F
    - Kidd, J G
    - Parsons, R J
  - Biological Reviews
  - Birmingham (England) University
    - C.G. Burton, 1938
    - Alan Gregg, 1939
    - R.E. Priestley, 1939
    - Eric W. Vincent, 1949
  - Bissing, Harry
  - Bitossi and Gonnella
  - Bittner, John J
  - Black, L M
  - Blacklock, John W S
  - Blair, W Frank
  - Blake, Francis G
  - Blake, Gwen
  - Blalock, Alfred
  - Blankenhorn, Marion Arthur
  - Blanton, Smiley
  - Blew, J Oscar
  - Bloch, Emile
  - Blogg, Minnie W
  - Bloom, David
  - Bloom, David
  - Bloom, Mrs. G M
  - Bloomfield, Arthur L
  - Bloor, W R
  - Bluemel, Mrs. Elinor
  - Blum, Theodor
  - Blumberg, Catherine W
  - Blumberg, Joe M
  - Blumenthal, Joseph
  - Blumer, George
  - Blumgart, Herrman L
  - Boardman, Bradley
  - Bobb, Mildred E
  - Bock, Fred G
  - Bodman, Mrs. E C
  - Bodman, Edward
    See also: Greene, James S.
  - Bodman, Herbert M
  - Bodman, Mrs. Theo
  - Bodo, Richard C
  - Bodrous Association
  - Bohme, Diethelm
  - Bohanan, C L
    - Fireside Homes, Inc., Aug. 29, 1921 July 1, 1921
  - Bolasco, Sergio
  - Bolker, Herman
  - Book of Knowledge
    See also: Flexner, Simon. April 6, 1934
  - Bootz, W F N
  - Bonne, C
  - Bonta, Maurice Buford
  - Booksellers
    - Baer, Joseph & Co.
    - Barnard, P M
    - Blackwell, B.H., Ltd.
    - Bookworm
    - Brown, Shipley & Co.
    - Bowes and Bowes
    - Breun, H
    - Brown, Frank R
    - Burnham Antique Book Store
    - Champion, H.
    - Commin, James G
    - Davenant Bookshop
    - David, G
    - Dobell, P.J. & A.E.
    - Edward, Francis
    - Galloway and Porter, Ltd.
    - George, William, Sons Ltd.
    - Giraudon
    - Glaisher, James
    - Goldsmith, Alfred F
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop
    - Grant, John & William
    - Guntrip, E [Guntrip & Richardson]
    - Heffer, W., & Sons, Ltd.
    - Howes, C
    - Johnson, Walter J., Inc.
    - Koehlers, K.F.
    - Login, B., & Son, Inc.
    - Lowe Brothers
    - Lull, Robert W
    - Michel, R G
    - Norman, F
    - Pearson, R.C.
    - Richardson, C
    - Salkeld, John
    - Sanders & Co.
    - Speyer & Peters
    - Stechert-Hafner, Inc.
    - Suckling & Co.
    - Webster, D
  - Boots, Ralph H
  - Borchard, Edwin M
  - Bordley, James, Jr.
  - Bornstein, David
  - Borrel, A
  - Bostick, W
  - Botsford, Elizabeth
  - Bouza, M
  - Bowden, C Philip
  - Bowden, Humphrey
  - Bowden, Philip
  - Bowman, Isaiah
  - Boyce, (Walter G. Bosia)
  - Boyce, Thomas K
  - Boycott, Arthur Edwin
  - Boycott, Constance L
  - Boycott, John
  - Boyd, William
  - Boyers, Luther Mussom
  - Boyse, Edward A
  - Brainin, Joseph
  - Branch, A
  - Branch, Charles F
  - Branion, H D
  - Brauer, Ralph W
  - Brecher, Ruth and Edward
  - Breck, Manley
  - Breeding and Laboratory Institute
  - Brendler, Herbert
  - Brennan, Elizabeth Mareble
  - Brick, Maurice
  - Bright, Mabel
  - Brimble, L John F
  - Brinkhous, K M
  - Briones & Co., Inc.
  - British Broadcasting Corporation
  - British Empire Cancer Campaign
  - British Medical Association
  - British Medical Journal
  - British Museum
  - Broadbent, Margaret
  - Brody, J C
  - Bronfenbrenner, J
  - Bronk, Detlev
  - Brooks, Barney
  - Brooks, Harlow
  - Brooks, Mrs. Van Wyck
  - Broome, John D
  - Broun, Goronwy Owen
  - Brower, Arthur Benedict
  - Brower, B V
  - Brown, E W
  - Brown, Frank A
  - Brown, Herbert R
  - Brown, Thomas R
  - Brown, Wade H
  - Browning, William
  - Bruda, Botho E K
  - Brues, Austin M
  - Brull, L
  - Brun, B Lucien
  - Brunero, Fusi
  - Brush, Edward N
  - Brussels. Belgian National League Against Cancer
  - Bruwer, Andre J
  - Bryan, W Ray
  - Buchanan, John
  - Buckley, Sonja M
  - Bulbs, Plants and Seeds
  - Bullock, Lewis T
  - Bullough, William S
  - Bunker, John W M
  - Bunting, C H
  - Burbank, Reginald
  - Burch, P R J
  - Burchell, Samuel C
  - Burk, Dean
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
  - Burke, Victor
  - Burkitt, Lymphoma
  - Burlingham, Charles C
  - Burlingham, Robert
  - Burls, A
  - Burmester, B R
  - Burnet, Sir F MacFarlane
  - Burnett, Vivian
  - Burns, Edward L
    General note
    [UNK] [UNK] 7-20-73
  - Burpee, W. Atlee Co.
  - Burrows, Montrose T
  - Burwell, C Sidney
  - Bury, Kenneth
  - Butler, Charles W
  - Butterfield, John
  - Bye, Mortimer
  - Byington, L B
  - Byrne, Eugene
  - C.H.A.T. Tours
  - Cairns, Sir Hugh
    - Witts, L J
    - Robb-Smith, Alastair
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Cairns, Margaret Patience
    - Stone, Frederick L
  - Caldwell, E V
  - Calhoun, J Alfred
  - Cambel, Plerihan
  - Cambridge U. - Trinity Hall
  - Cambridge University Press
    - Crutchley, Brooke
    - Mansbridge, F Ronald
    - Lancefield, Rebecca C
    - Eccleshare, C F
  - Cameron, Charles S
  - Cameron, Sir Roy
    - Crew, Alice
  - Campbell, Charles I
  - Campbell, Editha C
  - Campbell, J R Jr.
  - Campbell, Thomas F
  - Campo, A J
  - Cancer Congress
    - Woglom, William H
    - Wood, Francis Carter
  - Cancer Quacks
    - Collins, Mrs. A.M.
    - Davis, Willie
    - Dietrick, Ross E
    - Gregory, K M
    - Rondeau, G
  - Cancer Research (Cover), May 1967
  - Cancer Research [Journal]
    Contains ms. of article by P. Rous
    - Pohle, Elizabeth
    - Rusch, Harold P
    - Haddow, Alexander
  - "Cancer Research"
    - Cousins, W M
    - Golanski, Clarice
  - Cancer Research Round Table
    - Schram, Mrs. Mildred W S
  - Cancirco
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
    - Denues, A R T
  - Cane, Melville H
    - Proskauer, Joseph M
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
  - Cannan, R Keith
  - Cannel, Ed
  - Cannon, Paul R
  - Cannon, Walter Bradford
  - Cappell, D F
  - Cappelli, Carlo
  - Cappelli, John
  - Capps, Joseph A
  - Car & General Insurance Corp., Ltd. in re automobile accident, 1928
  - Carcinogenesis Abstracts
  - Carlo Erba Foundation
  - Carlson, A J
  - Carocari
  - Carr, J G
  - Carrel, Alexis
  - Carroll, B B
  - Carroll, Richard S
  - Cartaya, Luis
  - Carter, E P
  - Carter, Richard F
    - Porter, Keith
    - Michelson, Aaron I
  - Carworth Farms, C.N.W. Cumming
  - Casey, Albert E
  - Caspari, W
    - Cohn, Alfred E
    - Schwarz, Ernst
  - Caste, A
  - Castle, William B
  - Castroviejo, Ramon
  - Cattell, Henry W
  - Cattell, James McKeen
  - Central Committee for the Resettlement of Foreign Physicians
    See also: Committee for the Resettlement of Foreign Physicians
    - Jordan, Charles H
    - Kubie, Lawrence S
  - Central Hanover Bank & Trust Company
  - Central Union Trust Company
  - Century Association
    - Avery, Oswald T
    - Baekeland, L H
    - Northrop, John G
    - Swift, Homer
    - Palmer, Walter W
    - Willet, John A.P.
    - Merrill, Charles E., Jr.
    - Bogert, Marston T
    - Boots, Ralph E
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
    - Calkins, Gary N
    - Cannan, R Keith
    - Carrel, Alexis
    - Clarke, Hans
    - Cole, Rufus
    - Conant, James B
    - Conklin, E G
    - Coykendall, Frederick
    - Dakin, Henry D
    - Darrach, William
    - Dochez, A Raymond
    - Fairchild, B T
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Gay, Frederick P
    - Gregg, Alan
    - James, Henry
    - Kendall, James
    - Keppel, Frederick P
    - McGregor, James Howard
    - Miller, Edgar G., Jr.
    - Murphy, James B
    - Osterhout, W J V
    - Wilson, Edmund B
    - West, Randolph
    - Zinsser, Hans
    - Wyckoff, John
    - Prentice, T M
    - Moe, Henry Allen
    - Kinstler, Everett R
    - Marchand, P
    - Steele, J Murray
    - Corner, George Washington
    - MacLeod, Colin M
    - McDermott, Walsh
    - Cain, Walker O
    - McEwen, Currier
    - Smith, J Kellum
    - Taylor, Davidson
    - Lloyd, R McAllister
    - Hale, Robert Beverly
    - Burlingame, Roger
    - McIntosh, Rustin
    - Turner, Joseph C
    - Shope, Richard E
    - Burlingame, Charles C
    - Whipple, Allen O
    - Horan, Francis H
    - Delano, William Adams
    - Morgan, Thomas Hunt
    - MacKenzie, James C
    - Grouse
    - Northrop, John H
    - Knauth, Oswald W
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Brownell, George A
    - Purves, Austin, Jr.
    - Willcox, Bertram
    - Avery, O T
    - Dubois, Eugene
    - Ewing, Charles
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Hoagland, Charles L
    - Hopkins, J Gardner
    - Malloch, Archibald
    - Norton, William Warder
    - Opie, Eugene L
      [UNK]
    - Richards, Dickinson
    - Tarkington, Booth
    - West, Randolph
    - Wolfe, Paul A
    - Taylor, Howard C., Jr.
    - Rivers, Thomas M
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Acheson, Dean
    - Angell, James Howland
    - Barr, David
    - Carmichael, Leonard
    - Cave, Henry W
    - Day, George P
    - Donaldson, Norman V
    - Forkner, Claude E
    - French, Robert
    - Galpin, Perrin C
    - Hadley, Morris
    - Harrison, George L
    - Hewes, Thomas
    - Jay, Pierre
    - Nettleton, George H
    - Northrop, F S C
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Seymour, Charles
    - Valentine, Alan
    - Wadsworth, Augustus
    - Weed, Lewis H
    - Whitridge, Arnold
    - Wilder, Thornton
    - Winslow, C E A